<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker Swarm on Wes Shaddix | Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/tags/docker-swarm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker Swarm on Wes Shaddix | Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:53:37 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.wesshaddix.com/tags/docker-swarm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Ubuntu on Docker Swarm Node</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/upgrading-ubuntu-on-docker-swarm-node/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:53:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/upgrading-ubuntu-on-docker-swarm-node/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to document the steps needed to upgrade the OS of docker swarm nodes from Ubuntu 17.10 to Ubuntu 18.04
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing a Docker Swarm Cluster</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/visualizing-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 18:49:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/visualizing-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</guid>
      <description>[Updated] 12&amp;frasl;31 - Updated instructions to leverage the load balancer configuration that we added to the swarm cluster.
Goal In a previous blog post I setup a docker swarm cluster. Now I want a way to visualize what the swarm cluster looks like. How many nodes I have and which containers are running. Also as I change the state of the swarm cluster through docker commands I&amp;rsquo;d like to visualize what is actually happening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Node Docker Swarm with Ubuntu 17.04 on Azure</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/three-node-docker-swarm-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 17:31:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/three-node-docker-swarm-cluster/</guid>
      <description>[Updated] 12&amp;frasl;28 - Improved the setup so that we can use a load balancer in front of the swarm nodes as well as improve the availability of the swarm nodes
Overview I&amp;rsquo;m learning docker swarm mode and need a realistic simulation of setting up a multi-node cluster. Azure is an ideal platform to test things out. My goal is to create a docker swarm cluster within a single region. Creating a multi-region swarm cluster requires creating virutal networks in different regions and connecting those vnets through a vpn gateway which is not something I&amp;rsquo;m ready to tackle just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging and Monitoring on a Docker Swarm Cluster</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/logging-and-monitoring-on-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 19:11:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/logging-and-monitoring-on-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How to setup data analytics, metrics and events collection and logging on a docker swarm cluster using sematext SPM and Logsene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>