<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Wes Shaddix</title>
    <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Wes Shaddix</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License. Please give a reference to this source if you would like to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 17:31:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Swarm on Azure</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/docker-swarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 17:31:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/docker-swarm/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m learning docker swarm mode and need a realistic simulation of setting up a multi-node cluster. Azure is an ideal platform to test things out. My goal is to create a docker swarm cluster within a single region. Creating a multi-region swarm cluster requires creating virutal networks in different regions and connecting those vnets through a vpn gateway which is not something I&amp;rsquo;m ready to tackle just yet.
My Setup I&amp;rsquo;m running a windows 10 workstation with docker for windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showing UTF8 Characters in TeamCity 10 Build Logs</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/team-city-utf-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 21:43:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/team-city-utf-8/</guid>
      <description>As part of a continuous integration pipeline I&amp;rsquo;m running my Postman api tests after every deployment to our development environment via TeamCity and Newman. One issue that I encountered was that the TeamCity agent build log wasn&amp;rsquo;t showing formatted newman output correctly because by default it doesn&amp;rsquo;t show UTF8. In order to fix this you just have to update your C:\TeamCity\buildAgent\conf\buildAgent.properties file to include
teamcity.runner.commandline.stdstreams.encoding=UTF-8 and then restart the TeamCity Agent service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>