<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on Wes Shaddix</title>
    <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on Wes Shaddix</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License. Please give a reference to this source if you would like to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 19:11:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.wesshaddix.com/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging and Monitoring on a Docker Swarm Cluster</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/logging-and-monitoring-on-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 19:11:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/logging-and-monitoring-on-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How to setup data analytics, metrics and events collection and logging on a docker swarm cluster using sematext SPM and Logsene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing a Docker Swarm Cluster</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/visualizing-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 18:49:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/visualizing-a-docker-swarm-cluster/</guid>
      <description>Goal In a previous blog post I setup a docker swarm cluster. Now I want a way to visualize what the swarm cluster looks like. How many nodes I have and which containers are running. Also as I change the state of the swarm cluster through docker commands I&amp;rsquo;d like to visualize what is actually happening.
The solution There is a docker image named dockersamples/visualizer that will give you a url that you can go to in order to view your swarm cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Node Docker Swarm with Ubuntu Zesty 17.04 on Azure</title>
      <link>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/three-node-docker-swarm-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 17:31:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.wesshaddix.com/post/three-node-docker-swarm-cluster/</guid>
      <description>Overview I&amp;rsquo;m learning docker swarm mode and need a realistic simulation of setting up a multi-node cluster. Azure is an ideal platform to test things out. My goal is to create a docker swarm cluster within a single region. Creating a multi-region swarm cluster requires creating virutal networks in different regions and connecting those vnets through a vpn gateway which is not something I&amp;rsquo;m ready to tackle just yet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>